Now a tailor unzips a garment bag
and shows Salander a black leather jacket.
She compares it to Blomkvist’s jacket
in the photo of him and Erika.
As he zips the bag back up,
Salander gives a wistful look.
Now at her apartment,
she intently writes a message inside a card,
then slides it into an envelope.
The card's cover shows a horse bending its neck down
as a child bundled against the cold pats its head.
Salander writes an ‘M’ on the front of the envelope,
then underlines it.
She stares off.
Night-time.
Snow drifts to the ground
as Salander glides her motorcycle down a hill
and parks across the street
from Blomkvist’s apartment building.
Dismounting, she removes her helmet,
then takes the garment bag with her gift
off the bike's rear cargo rack.
She sees Blomkvist and Erika leaving the building
and watches unnoticed as he drapes
an arm over her shoulders.
The couple heads down a walkway
to a waiting taxi at the top of a hill.
Salander watches woundedly
as they climb into the cab,
then lowers her heartbroken gaze.
Turning away, she tosses Blomkvist’s gift
into a dumpster against the side of a building.
She glances at the cab as it drives off,
then dons her helmet
and mounts her bike.
She speeds off down the cobblestone street,
her figure disappearing from view as she rounds a corner.